Antonio Jaramillo Fanta

Madrid | EU Citizen | +34 609390315 | antoniojaramillofanta@gmail.com | English C1 | Spanish native

Objective

3-year experience as FrontEnd developer. Seeking a stable long-term position where I can develop professionally and solve coding requirements with my experience. As my previous experience in competitive sport, I have team vision, leadership and empathy.

Experience

STRENGTH, CONDITIONING AND BASKETBALL COACH | 2017-2021

· Coach for various teams across different age groups and skill levels, amateur and elite.

WEB DEVELOPER | CORUS CONSULTING | 2022

- · Develop & design a web application as part of a team for an entrepreneur using Vue and Quasar
- · Develop tests for a web application with playwright

WEB DEVELOPER | BBVA | 2023-NOW

- · Develop & design reusable web components in Lit for multiple projects
- · Assisted in the development of a React application using Redux
- · Develop a Vue/Quasar application for banking process management

Education

DOUBLE DEGREE IN SPORT SCIENCE (FINISHED) & PHYSIOTHERAPY (UNFINISHED) | 2020 | UNIVERSIDAD EUROPEA DE MADRID

· Speciality: High performance training

PROGRAMMING COURSES | 2021-2024 | ONLINE

- Programming for everybody (Python)
- Javascript
- · Vue | React | Lit

Skills

- · Front-end: Vue, React, Lit, Quasar, Typescript
- · **Testing:** Playwright
- · Methodologies: Agile, Scrum
- · Tools: Git, JIRA

Professional Skills

- Team collaboration & leadership
- · Client communication
- · Problem-solving
- · Fast learning & adaptation



